Bakke, E. Wight Papers 5522
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, General Contracting (Box 18, Folder 40)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, Commercial Headquarters (Box 18, Folder 41)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, Plant Headquarters (Box 18, Folder 42)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, Traffic Headquarters (Box 18, Folder 43)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, KRA Plant (Box 18, Folder 44)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, KRA Traffic (Box 18, Folder 45)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, Top (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Af - Union Officers, Accounting (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Af - Union Officers, Commercial Group I (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Af - Union Officers, Executive Board (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Af - Union Officers, Executive and Engineering (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Af - Union Officers, Plant Field (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Af - Union Officers, Traffic Field (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Af - Union Officers, Commercial Headquarters (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Af - Union Officers, Plant Headquarters (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Af - Union Officers, Traffic Headquarters (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Test Standards for Status System (Box 19, Folder 10)
- As - Definition Accounting, Employees (Box 19, Folder 11)
- As - Running Accounts, Accounting, Employees (Box 19, Folder 12)
- As - Employees, Commercial (Box 19, Folder 13)
- As - Employees, Commercial I - IV (Box 19, Folder 14)
- As - Employees, Commercial Directory (Box 19, Folder 15)
- As - Employees, Commercial Directory (Box 19, Folder 16)
- As - Employees, Running Accounts, Commercial Directory (Box 19, Folder 17)
- As - Employees, KRA, Commercial (Box 19, Folder 18)
- As - Employees, Running Accounts, District Engineers and Clerks (Box 19, Folder 19)
- As - Employees, Executive and General Engineering (Box 19, Folder 20)
- As - Employees, Headquarters, Commercial (Box 19, Folder 21)
- As - Employees, Headquarters, Commercial and Running Accounts (Box 19, Folder 22)
- As - Employees, Headquarters, Plant (Box 19, Folder 23)
- As - Employees, Headquarters, Plant (Box 19, Folder 24)
- As - Employees, Headquarters, Plant and Running Accounts (Box 19, Folder 25)
- As - Employees, Headquarters, Plant and Engineers KRA (Box 19, Folder 26)
- As - Employees, Headquarters, Traffic (Box 19, Folder 27)
- As - Employees, Inside and Outside Plant (Box 19, Folder 28)
- As - Employees, Inside Plant (Box 19, Folder 29)
- As - Employees, Inside Plant (copy) (Box 19, Folder 30)
- As - Employees, Inside Plant, New Haven (Box 19, Folder 31)
- As - Employees, Inside Plant, Group II (Box 19, Folder 32)
- As - Employees, Inside Plant, Group III (Box 19, Folder 33)
- As - Employees, Inside Plant, Group IV (Box 19, Folder 34)
- As - Employees, Inside Plant, All Groups (Box 19, Folder 35)
- As - Employees, Inside Plant, Running Accounts (Box 19, Folder 36)
- As - Employees, Inside Plant, Running Accounts (Box 19, Folder 37)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant (Box 19, Folder 38)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant (Box 19, Folder 39)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant (Box 19, Folder 40)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, New Haven, Hartford (Box 19, Folder 41)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Stamford, Waterbury, New Britain (Box 19, Folder 42)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Group III (Box 19, Folder 43)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Group IV (Box 20, Folder 1)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Group IV (Box 20, Folder 2)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Running Accounts (Box 21, Folder 1)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Running Accounts (Box 21, Folder 2)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Running Accounts (Box 21, Folder 3)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Running Accounts (Box 21, Folder 4)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Running Accounts (Box 21, Folder 5)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Traffic (Box 21, Folder 6)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Traffic, New Haven, Hartford (Box 21, Folder 7)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Traffic, Waterbury, Stamford, New Britain (Box 21, Folder 8)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Traffic, Danbury, Norwich, Torrington (Box 21, Folder 9)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Traffic, Willamantic, Saybrook, Putnam (Box 21, Folder 10)
- As - Employees, Outside Plant, Traffic, Groups III and IV (Box 21, Folder 11)
- As - Employees, Traffic, Group IV (Box 21, Folder 12)
- As - Employees, Traffic, Running Accounts (Box 21, Folder 13)
- As - Definition Management, Commercial Department (Box 21, Folder 14)
- As - Management, Commercial, District and Division (Box 21, Folder 15)
- As - Management, Commercial, Group I (Box 21, Folder 16)
- As - Management, Commercial, Group II (Box 21, Folder 17)
- As - Management, Commercial, Group II - IV, KRA (Box 21, Folder 18)
- As - Management, District and Division, Engineers (Box 21, Folder 19)
- As - Management, District and Division, Engineers, Running Accounts (Box 21, Folder 20)
- As - Management, Executive Department (Box 21, Folder 21)
- As - Management, Executive Department, KRAs (Box 21, Folder 22)
- As - Management, Headquarters, Commercial Department (Box 21, Folder 23)
- As - Management, Headquarters, General Engineering (Box 21, Folder 24)
- As - Management, Headquarters, General Engineering, KRA (Box 21, Folder 25)
- As - Management, Headquarters, Plant Management (Box 21, Folder 26)
- As - Management, Headquarters, Plant Management (Box 21, Folder 27)
- As - Management, Headquarters, Plant Management, Running Accounts (Box 21, Folder 28)
- As - Management, Headquarters, Plant Management, KRA (Box 21, Folder 29)
- As - Management, Headquarters, Traffic (Box 21, Folder 30)
- As - Management, Headquarters, Traffic, Running Accounts (Box 21, Folder 31)
- As - Management, Plant Department, District and Division (Box 21, Folder 32)
- As - Management, Plant, Group I (Box 21, Folder 33)
- As - Management, Inside Plant, Group I and II (Box 21, Folder 34)
- As - Management, Inside Plant, Group II and III (Box 21, Folder 35)
- As - Management, Inside Plant, Group I - 4 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- As - Management, Inside Plant (Box 21, Folder 37)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Inside Plant, Group B (Box 22, Folder 1)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Inside Plant, New Haven (Box 22, Folder 2)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Inside Plant, Hartford (Box 22, Folder 3)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Inside Plant, Stamford (Box 22, Folder 4)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Inside Plant, Waterbury (Box 22, Folder 5)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Inside Plant, New Britain (Box 22, Folder 6)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Inside Plant, Danbury (Box 22, Folder 7)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Inside Plant, Torrington (Box 22, Folder 8)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Inside Plant, Norwich (Box 22, Folder 9)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Inside Plant, Inside Plant Field Employees (Box 22, Folder 10)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Outside Plant, New Haven (Box 22, Folder 11)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Outside Plant, Hartford (Box 22, Folder 12)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Outside Plant, Stamford (Box 22, Folder 13)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Outside Plant, Waterbury (Box 22, Folder 14)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Outside Plant, New Britain (Box 22, Folder 15)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Outside Plant, Danbury (Box 22, Folder 16)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Outside Plant, Torrington (Box 22, Folder 17)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Outside Plant, Norwich (Box 22, Folder 18)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Outside Plant, Outside Plant Employees (Box 22, Folder 19)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Outside Plant, Outside Plant Field Employees (Box 22, Folder 20)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Traffic, Torrington, Groups 4 and 5 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Traffic, Group 4 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Traffic, Group 5 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Traffic, New Haven (Box 22, Folder 24)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Traffic, Hartford (Box 22, Folder 25)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Traffic, Stamford (Box 22, Folder 26)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Traffic, Waterbury (Box 22, Folder 27)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Traffic, New Britain (Box 22, Folder 28)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Traffic, Danbury (Box 22, Folder 29)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Traffic, Torrington (Box 22, Folder 30)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Traffic, Norwich (Box 22, Folder 31)
- C1 - C11, Employees, Traffic, Traffic Field Employees, Summary (Box 22, Folder 32)
- C1 - C11, Management, Accounting (Box 23, Folder 1)
- C1 - C11, Management, Accounting (Box 23, Folder 2)
- C1 - C11, Management, Commercial, Group I (Box 23, Folder 3)
- C1 - C11, Management, Commercial, Group II (Box 23, Folder 4)
- C1 - C11, Management, Commercial, Group III (Box 23, Folder 5)
- C1 - C11, Management, Commercial, Group IV (Box 23, Folder 6)
- C1 - C11, Management, Commercial, District and Division (Box 23, Folder 7)
- C1 - C11, Commercial, Field Management, Summary (Box 23, Folder 8)
- C1 - C11, Management, Headquarters, Commercial (Box 23, Folder 9)
- C1 - C11, Management, Headquarters, Directory (Box 23, Folder 10)
- C1 - C11, Management, Headquarters, Executive Management (Box 23, Folder 11)
- C1 - C11, Management, Headquarters, Executive Management, Charts (Box 23, Folder 12)
- C1 - C11, Management, Headquarters, General Engineering (Box 23, Folder 13)
- C1 - C11, Management, Headquarters, General Engineering, Charts (Box 23, Folder 14)
- C1 - C7, Management, Headquarters, Plant (Box 23, Folder 15)
- C8, Management, Headquarters, Plant (Box 23, Folder 16)
- C1 - C10, Management, Headquarters, Traffic (Box 23, Folder 17)
- C4 - C11, Management, Headquarters, Traffic (Box 23, Folder 18)
- C1 - C3, Management, Headquarters, Traffic, Charts (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Communications, Management, Headquarters, District and Division, Engineers (Box 23, Folder 20)
- C1 - C11, Management, Headquarters, District, Division, Engineers, New Haven (Box 23, Folder 21)
- C1 - C11, Management, Headquarters, District, Division, Hartford (Box 23, Folder 22)
- C1 - C11, Management, Headquarters, District, Division, New Britain, Stamford (Box 23, Folder 23)
- C1 - C11, Management, Headquarters, District, Division, Waterbury (Box 23, Folder 24)
- C1 - C11, Management, Inside Plant, Group I (Box 23, Folder 25)
- C1 - C11, Management, Inside Plant, Group II (Box 23, Folder 26)
- C1 - C11, Management, Inside Plant, Group III (Box 23, Folder 27)
- C1 - C11, Management, Inside Plant, Group IV (Box 23, Folder 28)
- C1 - C11, Management, Inside Plant, Management Summary (Box 23, Folder 29)
- C1 - C11, Management, Outside Plant, Group I (Box 24, Folder 1)
- C1 - C11, Management, Outside Plant, Group II (Box 24, Folder 2)
- C1 - C11, Management, Outside Plant, Group III (Box 24, Folder 3)
- C1 - C11, Management, Outside Plant, Group IV (Box 24, Folder 4)
- C1 - C11, Management, Outside Plant, Summary (Box 24, Folder 5)
- C1 - C11, Management, Traffic, Group I (Box 24, Folder 6)
- C1 - C11, Management, Traffic, Group II (Box 24, Folder 7)
- C1 - C11, Management, Traffic, Group III (Box 24, Folder 8)
- C1 - C11, Management, Traffic, Group IV and V (Box 24, Folder 9)
- C1 - C11, Management, Traffic, Summary (Box 24, Folder 10)
- C1 - C11, Management, Traffic, District and Division (Box 24, Folder 11)
- C1 - C9, Management, Top (Box 24, Folder 12)
- C1 - C11, Management, Top, Charts (Box 24, Folder 13)
- C1 - C10, Union Officers, Commercial Field (Box 24, Folder 14)
- C1 - C10, Union Officers, Commercial Field, Charts (Box 24, Folder 15)
- C10, Union Members, Commercial, Group I - IV (Box 24, Folder 16)
- C10, Union Officers, Executive Department (Box 24, Folder 17)
- C10, Union Officers, Executive Department (Box 24, Folder 18)
- C1 - C10, Union Officers, Headquarters (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Final Write-ups to be done on U.O. Traffic and Commercial (Box 24, Folder 20)
- C1 - C10, Union Officers, Plant Field (Box 24, Folder 21)
- C10, Union Officers, Plant Group II (Box 24, Folder 22)
- C10, Union Officers, Plant Group III - IV (Box 24, Folder 23)
- C1 - C10, Union Officers, Plant, Charts (Box 24, Folder 24)
- C1 - C10, Union Officers, Traffic Field (Box 24, Folder 25)
- C10, Union Officers, Traffic, Groups I and II (Box 24, Folder 26)
- C10, Union Officers, Traffic, Groups III, IV, V (Box 24, Folder 27)
- C1 - C10, Union Officers, Traffic Field, Charts (Box 24, Folder 28)
- R + P, Employee, Commercial (Box 25, Folder 1)
- R + P, Employee, Commercial (Box 25, Folder 2)
- R + P, Employee, Headquarters, New Haven (Box 25, Folder 3)
- R + P, Employee, Headquarters, New Haven, (Executives) (Box 25, Folder 4)
- R + P, Employee, Outside and Inside Plant (Box 25, Folder 5)
- R + P, Employee, Inside and Outside, New Haven, Stamford, Hartford, Waterbury (Box 25, Folder 6)
- R + P, Employee, Inside and Outside, New Britain, Norwich, Danbury, Torrington (Box 25, Folder 7)
- R + P, Employee, Inside and Outside, Group IV (Box 25, Folder 8)
- R + P, Employee, Traffic Supervisors and Operators (Box 25, Folder 9)
- R + P, Employee, Data for use in preparing summaries for ... (Box 25, Folder 10)
- R + P, Employee, Instructions for Final Summary (Box 25, Folder 11)
- R + P, Employee, Summary: Commercial, I.P., Traffic (Box 25, Folder 12)
- R + P, Employee, Summary: Commercial, I.P., Traffic (2) (Box 25, Folder 13)
- R + P, Management, Headquarters, Charts (Box 25, Folder 14)
- R + P, Management, Inside Plant, Groups I - IV (Box 25, Folder 15)
- R + P, Management, Outside Plant, Groups I - IV (Box 25, Folder 16)
- R + P, Management, Top Management (Box 25, Folder 17)
- R + P, Management, Traffic, Groups I - IV (Box 25, Folder 18)
- R + P, Union Officers, Communications (Box 25, Folder 19)
- R + P, Union Officers, Inside and Outside Plant (Box 25, Folder 20)
- R + P, Union Officers, Inside and Outside Plant, Stamford, New Haven, Waterbury, Hartford (Box 25, Folder 21)
- R + P, Union Officers, Operators and Clerks, Supervisors and Traffic (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Organizational Charter, Employee, Headquarters (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Organizational Charter, Employee, Traffic (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Organizational Charter, Employee Company, Definition and KRA's (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Organizational Charter, Employees, Field Department, Group I (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Organizational Charter, Employees, Field Department, Group II (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Organizational Charter, Employees, Field Department, Group III (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Organizational Charter, Employees, Field Department, Group IV and V (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Organizational Charter, Employees, Union, New Britain, Torrington, Hartford, Waterbury, Norwich, Group B (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Organizational Charter, Management (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Organizational Charter, Management, Company (Plant, Traffic, Communications) (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Organizational Charter, Management, Division and District I - IV, Hartford, New Haven, New Britain, Waterbury, Stamford, Torrington (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Organizational, Union (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Organizational, Union, Terms (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Organizational, Union, Terms, New Britain, Hartford, New Haven, Stamford, Waterbury, Danbury, Norwich, Group IV (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Organizational, Union, Group I - IV, New Haven, Hartford (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Organizational, Union, Group II, Stamford, Waterbury, New Britain (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Organizational, Union, Group III (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Organizational, Union, Group IV (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Interview Notes and Responses (Box 26, Folder 1)
  re: SNETCO Study: Eastern Division: Hartford Division, New Britain, New London District, Western Division, Bridgeport District, New Haven District, Stamford District, Waterbury District
- Interview Notes and Responses (Box 26, Folder 2)
  re: SNETCO Study: General Engineering
- Interview Notes and Responses (Box 27, Folder 1)
  re: SNETCO Study: Headquarters-Accounting
- Interview Notes and Responses (Box 27, Folder 2)
  re: SNETCO Study: Management-Plant: Stamford, Waterbury, New Britain, Danbury
- Interview Notes and Responses (Box 28, Folder 1)
  re: SNETCO Study: Management-Plant continued: Norwich, Torrington, Willamantic, Saybrook, Putnam, Canaan
- Interview Notes and Responses (Box 28, Folder 2)
  re: SNETCO Study: House Service I, 12th Ward
- Interview Notes and Responses (Box 29, Folder 1)
  re: SNETCO Study: Miscellaneous: Goals, Secretaries, Dining Service, H. Service II; Headquarters: R21, R13, Goals, Secretary-Stenographer Div. pl. checking dining service employees; House Service, Part II
- Interview Notes and Responses (Box 29, Folder 2)
  re: SNETCO Study: Executive Management
- Interview Notes and Responses (Box 30, Folder 1)
  re: SNETCO Study: Management, Plant Headquarters
- Interview Notes and Responses (Box 30, Folder 2)
  re: SNETCO Study: Management Plant: New Haven, Hartford
- Interview Notes and Responses (Box 31, Folder 1)
  re: SNETCO Study: Norwich: Traffic, Commercial, Inside Plant, Outside Plant
- The Mutual Survival Research Trip, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Norwegian Contribution to Management Development (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Administrativt Forskningsfond (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Administrativt Forskningsfond (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Administrativt Forskningsfond (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Administrativt Forskningsfond, 4a (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Administrativt Forskningsfond, 4b (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Administrativt Forskningsfond, 5a (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Administrativt Forskningsfond, 5b (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Administrativt Forskningsfond, 6 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Administrativt Forskningsfond, 7 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Norwegian Cases (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Norwegian Consultation Bergen (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Source Book of Personnel Forms (NFI) (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Ford Foundation, 1951-1952 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Accounting Department, #11.3-1, 11.3-2, 11.3-3, 11.3-4 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Allen (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Analysis Department, #11.4-1, 11.4-2, 11.4-3, 11.4-4 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Auditing Department, #11.1, 11.2-1, 11.2-2 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Bank Study, Approach to Management (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Bank Study Report (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Block Department, #10.4-46, 10.4-47, 10.4-53, 10.4-56, 10.4-57 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Bookkeeping Department (1) (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Bookkeeping Department (2) (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Bookkeeping Department Report (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Broadway Office (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Central Files (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Check Files S.D., 10.4-60, 10.4-65, 10.4-62 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Cleaver, Head of Trust Department (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Collection Department, 10.5-1, 10.5-2, 10.5-3, 10.5-4, 10.5-5 (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Crawford (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Credit Department and Loan, 9.2-1, 9.2-2, 9.2-3, 9.2-4, 9.2-5 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Discount Department, 9.1, 9.3-1, 9.3-2, 9.3-3 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- East Haven Branch (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Foreign Exchange (Box 32, Folder 35)
- General File (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Hooker (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Installment Loan Department, 9.4-1, 9.4-2, 9.4-2a, 9.4-3a, 9.4-3c (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Interviews #8 - #13 - F.N.B., 1952 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  Nov. 4th
- Interviews #8 - #13 - F.N.B., 1952 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Interviews #8 - #13 - F.N.B., 1952 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Interviews #8 - #13 - F.N.B., 1952 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Interviews #8 - #13 - F.N.B., 1952 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Interviews #8 - #13 - F.N.B., 1952 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Interviews #14 - F.N.B., 1952 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  Nov. 5th
- Investment Department #8.5-1, #8.5-2 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Observations in the Bookkeeping Department (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Officers (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Safe Deposit Department and Mail #10.3-2 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Savings Department, 12.1, 12.2-1, 12.2-3, 12.3-1, 11.3-2, 12.3-4, 12.3-6 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Summary Notes on the Savings Department (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Supply and Stock Department, #11.5-1, 11.5-2, 11.5-3 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Tellers 10.2-3 thru 10.2-21 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Trust Department (1) (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Trust Department (2) (Box 33, Folder 19)
- West Haven Branch (Box 33, Folder 20)
- American Saw and Tool Company (Box 33, Folder 21)
- American Saw and Tool Company (Box 33, Folder 22)
- American Saw and Tool Company, Report (Box 33, Folder 23)
- American Saw and Tool Company, State of Organization (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Fort Atkinson Study (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Industrial and Personnel Relations, Director's Report 1959-60 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Memos, Reports, etc. (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Milwaukee Conference (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Motorola (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Thomas Industries (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Thomas Industries (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Thomas Industries (Box 33, Folder 33)
- Thomas Industries (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Thomas Industries, Conference of Personnel Officers, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 35)
- Thomas Industries, Conference of Personnel Officers, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 36)
- Thomas Industries, Current (Box 33, Folder 37)
- Thomas Industries, Current Salary Adv. (Box 33, Folder 38)
- Thomas Industries, Current with Personnel People (Box 33, Folder 39)
- Thomas Industries, Development of Evaluation Form (Box 33, Folder 40)
- Thomas Industries, History (Box 33, Folder 41)
- Thomas Industries, Management Development (Box 33, Folder 42)
- Thomas Industries, Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 33, Folder 43)
- Thomas Industries, Policy (Box 33, Folder 44)
- Thomas Industries, Top Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 45)
- Vermont Tap and Die (Box 33, Folder 46)
- Vermont Tap and Die (Box 33, Folder 47)
- Vermont Tap and Die (Box 33, Folder 48)
- Vermont Tap and Die, Scanlon (Box 33, Folder 49)
- Vermont Tap and Die, Survey, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 50)
- Altbach, Philip G., India (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Altbach, Edith H., Students in Revolutions of 1848 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Bachtiar, Harsja W., Indonesian Students and Their Political Activities (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Bakke, E. Wight, Mass Demonstrations: Mexico, Columbia, Japan, India (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Bereday, George Z. F., Montreal, Ibadan, Warsaw, Rangoon (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Conference on Students and Politics at University of Puerto Rico (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Congolese Students and Politics (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Cornell, Richard, Students and Politics in Communist Countries of Eastern Europe (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Douglas, Stephen G., Students and Politics in Indonesia (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Fields, G. Belden, French Student Movement (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Finlay, David J., University of Ghana (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Glazer, Myron, Political Attitudes and Activities of Chilean University Students (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Halsey, A. H. and Stephen Marks, British Student Politics (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Hanna, William John and Judith Lynne, Notes on Political... (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Hegarty, Thomas and Louisa, Student Movements at Russian University (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Inglese, Juan Osvaldo, Argentina (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Israel, John, Reflections on Modern Chinese Student Movements (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Lepper, John G., Student Politics in the Philippines (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Lipset, Seymour M. and Philip Altbach, Western Countries and U.S. (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Moore, Clement H. and Arlie Hochschild, North Africa (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Occupational Revolution, Copy 2, Chapters 1 - 7 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Occupational Revolution, Copy 2, Chapters 1 - 7 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Oh, Byung Hun, University Students and Politics in Korea (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Peterson, Richard E., Student Left in American Higher Education (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Piriner, Frank A., Transition and Transgression (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Rooks, Charles S., University Students in Politics in Nigeria (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Roos, Leslie L., Nordlou Roos and Gary Fields, Students and Politics in Turkey (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Scott, Robert E., Latin America: Peru and Mexico (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Shimbori, Michiya, Sociology of a Student Movement - Zengakuren: A Japanese Case (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Silverstein, Josef, Burmese Student Politics in a Changing Society (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Soares, Glaucio, World of Ideology (Box 34, Folder 31)